YUSUKE KOMINAMI

+81-90-6199-9337

yukke.konan@gmail.com

Education

Kyoto University

B.S. Biology (Mar 2020)

Main area: Bioinformatics and image processing with machine learning.

Research: research theme is super resolution of images taken with electronic microscope.

Swiss Federal Institute of Technology in Lausanne, faculty of Computer Science

Study abroad (Aug 2018 - Dec 2018)

Skills

- Algorithm design for machine learning.
- Python, C, C++, Common Lisp, Java, etc.
- Graphic Libraries
- Pytorch
- Project Management

Profile

I am Yusuke Kominami. I graduated from the faculty of Science in Kyoto University, majored Biology. My main research was image processing and reinforcement learning, and I am better at software engineering than biology. About software engineering, my expertise ranges from HTML/CSS/JavaScript to low-level programming. And I have solid knowledge on machine learning and statistics based on mathematics.

Experience

SoftBank — April, 2020 - Present Machine Learning Engineer; NLP.

Aiful - May, 2019 - Present

Part-time engineer. Software Engineer and Project Manager. Built office system with Python, Django, GCP and AWS.

LINE - August, 2019

Summer Internship. Made a small Web application in a week.

Flywheel - August, 2019 - September, 2019

Summer Internship: Data Scientist and Machine Learning Engineer. Built a recommendation algorithm in EC and optimized advertisement delivery system.

ABEJA - June, 2019 - July, 2019

Machine Learning Intern. Implemented object detection algorithms.

Hitachi — June, 2017 - July, 2018

Machine Learning Research Intern. Main area was Reinforcement Learning.

Links

GitHub: https://github.com/komi1230

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yusuke-kominami-0419b1157/

Portfolio: https://komi1230.github.io

Twitter: https://twitter.com/komi_edtr_1230